Class of 1911 Records, 1907-1976
Smith College Archives
Class of 1911 Records
1907-1976
Smith College. Class of 1911.
RG 80 UUID:6ab9e1d9-d756-4def-a946-5e758c89c852
20 boxes (9.8 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 20 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1911.
The Class of 1911 was the thirty-third entering class and the thirty-third graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1911 records, 1907-1976, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1911, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1911 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Baccalaureate Service 1911 (Box 1771, Folder 1)
- Bat 1911 (Box 1771, Folder 2)
- Collation 1911 (Box 1771, Folder 3)
- Commencement 1911 (Box 1771, Folder 4)
- Commencement Music 1911 (Box 1771, Folder 5)
- Freshman Grind 1907 (Box 1771, Folder 6)
- Freshman Frolic 1907 (Box 1771, Folder 7)
- Freshman Handbook 1907 (Box 1771, Folder 8)
- Groups 1907-1911 (Box 1771, Folder 9)
- Insignia, Numerals undated (Box 1772, Folder 1)
- History 1907-1961 (Box 1772, Folder 2)
- Ivy Day 1911 (Box 1772, Folder 3)
- Ivy Day Photographs 1911 (Box 1772, Folder 4)
- Junior Prom 1910 (Box 1772, Folder 5)
- Junior Prom Garden Party 1910 (Box 1772, Folder 6)
- Junior Ushers 1910 (Box 1772, Folder 7)
- Class Letters 1911-1976 (Box 1773, Folder 1)
- Reunions, General undated (Box 1773, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1912-1913 (Box 1773, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1914 (Box 1773, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1916 (Box 1773, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1921-1925 (Box 1773, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1928-1931 (Box 1773, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1936 (Box 1773, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1941 (Box 1773, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1946 (Box 1773, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1951 (Box 1773, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1956 (Box 1773, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1961 (Box 1773, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1975-1976 (Box 1773, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1966-1976 (Box 1773, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1981 (Box 1773, Folder 16)
- Reunion Songs undated (Box 1773, Folder 17)
- Senior Dramatics- Music 1911 (Box 1773, Folder 18)
- Senior Dramatics Photographs 1911 (Box 1774, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics Photographs 1911 (Box 1774, Folder 2)
- Senior Dramatics Photographs 1911 (Box 1774, Folder 3)
- Songs undated (Box 1774, Folder 4)
- Sophomore Reception 1909 (Box 1774, Folder 5)
- Statistics undated (Box 1774, Folder 6)
- Statistics- War Service 1941-1946 (Box 1774, Folder 7)
- Class Supper 1911 (Box 1774, Folder 8)
- Year Book 1911 (Box 1774, Folder 9)
- Unidentified 1960, undated (Box 1774, Folder 10)
- Class Secretary's Records, A-Bar (Box 1775, Folder 1)
- Class Secretary's Records, Bas-Br (Box 1775, Folder 2)
- Class Secretary's Records, Bu-C (Box 1775, Folder 3)
- Class Secretary's Records, Col-El (Box 1775, Folder 4)
- Class Secretary's Records, Est-God (Box 1775, Folder 5)
- Class Secretary's Records, Go-Hu (Box 1775, Folder 6)
- Class Secretary's Records, I-Little (Box 1775, Folder 7)
- Class Secretary's Records, Lloyd-Mills (Box 1775, Folder 8)
- Class Secretary's Records, Mo-Pat (Box 1775, Folder 9)
- Class Secretary's Records, Pe-Ri (Box 1775, Folder 10)
- Class Secretary's Records, Ro-She (Box 1776, Folder 1)
- Class Secretary's Records, Shi-Tho (Box 1776, Folder 2)
- Reunion Memorabilia, Class Scrapbook (Box OV)